

ALEXANDRE CALIARO

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

PROFIL

I honed my skills at Axiocode, rocking Angular for 2 years, before diving into the e-commerce realm with my own venture. Image:

Intrigued by the Blockchain magic, I embarked on a journey at Alyra, shaping up as a Blockchain developer.

CONTACT

Tel. +33 6 14 99 09 59 Metz, France caliaro.alexandre@gmail.com https://alexandre-caliaro.vercel.app

SKILLS

- Next.js / React
- Angular
- Typescript
- Solidity
- Symfony
- SQL Server
- French (Native language)
- English (Professional)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Temporary assignments • 2020-2023

Various positions in diverse fields such as agri-food factories, automobile factories, construction, archaeology, network installation...

Self-employed • 2019

Creation, online deployment, and maintenance of a Shopify website

Axiocode • 2016-2019

Web developer analyst (focused on Angular/Symfony)

FORMATION

Alyra School • 2023

Certificate in Web Developer and Integrator 3.0

NumericALL WF3 School • 2016

Certificate in Web Developer and Integrator 2.0

Louis Bertrand High School • 2013-2014

Scientific Baccalaureate (option in Computer Science and Digital Science - ISN)